footballfans.eu 2016-11-29

# Privacy policy

FootballFans.eu (`FootballFans´) is an initiative of Itude Sports Interattractive B.V., Chamber of Commerce, no. 30245045, and having its registered office at Kosterijland 70-78, 3981 AJ Bunnik in The Netherlands. The email address that can be used to reach us is [info@footballfans.eu](mailto:info@footballfans.eu).  
The storage of your personal data is registered at the Dutch Data Protection Authority (CBP) with number M1414221.

By using or accessing our website, www.FootballFans.eu, (“Website”) you are accepting the conditions of this privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”).

FootballFans works hard to earn and keep its user´s trust. Therefore FootballFans strictly adheres to the following principles to protect the user´s privacy.

FootballFans collects, processes, and uses all data and/or information about and related to the user´s person and the user´s account with FootballFans (“Personal Data”) in accordance with the applicable laws and statutes on data protection of the Netherlands and those of the European Union.

FootballFans uses Personal Data solely to provide the user with the services of FootballFans (“Services”) or to send you information about our Services such as updates. We will never rent, sell, or otherwise provide Personal Data to any third party for advertising or for marketing purposes without the user´s consent.

In principle, FootballFans does not require you to provide personal information in order to have access to, or view our Website.   
However, in order to provide you with all the Services given under the Website, you must create an account and provide us with your e-mail address, a password that you will use for your account and other specified information. We will send an email to your e-mail address to instruct you how to confirm your registration.

Children and minors under the age of 16 are not eligible to use any FootballFans Service and are therefore not allowed to submit any personal information to FootballFans, unless they have prior consent of their parent(s) and/or legal guardians. Parents and/or legal guardians are responsible for the protection of their children´s privacy. When creating an account under the age of 16 and accepting the conditions as set out in this Privacy Statement, you guarantee that you have got the aforementioned consent of your parent(s) and/or legal guardians.

When you create an account on FootballFans, you submit personal information to us through the Website. Personal information consists of different types of information, such as your username and e-mail address (required information), your name, postal address and details of your personal website (optional). Should you choose to use the services of the FootballFans Collectors Corner (optional), we will require you to submit financial details as well. If you communicate with us via e-mail or post messages to a forum, this too may be collected as personal information.

We will use your personal information to improve our Services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Website´s services that you are authorized to access.

Only when you specifically agree, your personal information will be shared with third parties, for instance to provide you with FootballFans affiliated news or offers.

FootballFans will never ask you for your login or other personally identifiable information via e-mail, instant messages or pop-up. If you witness any of these possible scams, please ignore them and inform FootballFans.

FootballFans collects other information than the personal information mentioned before. We collect the following information when you visit our Website: IP address, domain servers, types of computers accessing the Website and types of web browsers that are used to access the Website. This data is strictly anonymous information that is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving the Website.

We also use cookies. A cookie is a small text file used for different purposes, for example to store your password. This way you don´t have to re-enter it each time you visit FootballFans. Some of our advertisers or other third parties may also use cookies on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies since this Privacy Statement is only applicable to the use of cookies by FootballFans.

At any time, you may revise your account and the personal information at FootballFans. Through your Change settings page you can view and update the personal information that we have already collected and choose whether or not you wish us to send you announcements like newsletters or special offers.

To access Change settings, log in to your account and navigate to the My profile tab and click `Change settings´ If you require assistance in updating and/or correcting your personal information, please use the Contact link or send an e-mail to [info@FootballFans.eu](mailto:info@FootballFans.eu).

You can, at any time, delete your account and/or delete content you posted on the Website or request FootballFans to do so. To revoke your account, you can send us an e-mail and we will delete your account. When revoking your user account, you have two options: to leave your posted content on the site, or to remove all your content. With the first option, your user account and posted content will be made anonymous. With the second option your personal information and posted content will not be displayed anymore after the deletion of your account.

By Dutch Law however, we are obligated to retain your personal information for at least 6 months. Your personal information will therefore be stored on the FootballFans servers, even after deletion or termination of your account.

Personal information should be treated and stored in a secured manner. Apart from the fact that FootballFans uses SSL to offer secure communications by encrypting personal information to and from the Website, our servers are based in a secure environment behind a dedicated firewall. Access to the (personal) information contained in this secure environment is restricted with encryption and passwords. The password you choose to secure your account, is saved in a coded manner. No one at FootballFans or Itude Sports Interattractive B.V. has access to your password.

The personal information you provide to FootballFans is not visible for search engines, except for your username and public information such as your country, your website information, reports, videos and photos you may post.

As stated, FootballFans protects your personal information, both during transmission and in storage. It is however impossible to guarantee its absolute security, although we take all the necessary and appropriate measures within our capabilities.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can contact us via the Contact link at each page, or send an e-mail to us at [info@footballfans.eu](mailto:info@footballfans.eu).

We will comply with demands made by law enforcement or other governmental officials in response to a verified request relating a criminal investigation.

When creating an account, you agree that certain personal information (pointed out under Security of your Personal Data) of your account will be visible for other users of the Website.

You understand and acknowledge that every time you use FootballFans by adding material or information for others to see, this can become public. When adding material like photos, videos or comments and reports, you should be aware that anything you submit can be read, collected, or used by others that visit the Website, and can as a result be used to send you unsolicited messages. You should therefore understand and acknowledge that whenever you provide information as described (by entering messages, posting photos, videos, comments and reports), you do so at your own risk.

FootballFans is not responsible for the Personal information you choose to share with others via our Website, and cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share data and information. Therefore, FootballFans cannot and does not guarantee that personal information, user content, and other information the user posts on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. FootballFans is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the FootballFans Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of personal information, user content, and other information may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored this data and information.

The FootballFans Website may contain links or referrals to other websites. Since we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content stored on other websites, please understand that any information that is provided by you to these other websites may become public information. You should always be cautious when providing others with personal information.

If you choose to invite friends to FootballFans via FootballFans.eu, the names and e-mail addresses of the invitees will need to be entered on the Website. The names and e-mail addresses of the people that are invited will be used by FootballFans only to send an invitation e-mail (including an optional personal message) and corresponding reminders. FootballFans stores this information to send the invitation e-mail, to register a contact connection if the invitation is accepted, and to track the success of the FootballFans referral program.

For technical and operational reasons it may be necessary for your (personal) information to be transferred to (servers of) companies affiliated to us and/or advertisers to countries outside the European Union (EU), where the regulations in the field of privacy protection might not provide the same protection as in the EU. Insofar as this is necessary, you hereby agree that your (personal) information can be transferred to countries outside the EU.

FootballFans reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, for instance to comply with changes in law or to reflect industry initiatives, so please review it frequently. If we change our privacy policy, we will inform you of the changes made when logging on to your account the first time after these changes take effect. We will require you to accept these changes prior to completing the log in process.

We take your privacy very seriously. If you feel we are violating your privacy in any way or if you have questions that are not answered in this Privacy Statement, you can contact us by using the Contact link, by sending an e-mail to or writing to FootballFans, Itude Sports Interattractive B.V. , Kosterijland 70-78, 3981 AJ in Bunnik, The Netherlands.
